# Mariani

# Front End Web Developer

Front End Developer with 4 years experience delivering highly responsive web for diverse industry organizations. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript plus modern libraries and frameworks. Aspiring to offer the best user experience through efficient website development.

## **Experience**

Nov. 2019 - May 2021

## Front End Web Manager @PT Global Coding Indonesia, Malang

- Manage a small development team consisting of 5 frontend developers.
- Research and implement technology best practices appropriately into web development.
- Provide solutions for web development issues.

Jul. 2017 - Nov. 2019

## Front End Web Developer @PT Global Coding Indonesia, Malang

- Transform user interface designs into front-end code with HTML, CSS & Javascript.
- Work with back-end developers to integrate UI components with APIs and databases.
- · Maintain and update websites.
- Quality-test, debug errors and troubleshoot the website and/or its applications in various browsers.

Jul. 2015 - Mar. 2016

Ul Engineer @Lab Mobile FILKOM Brawijaya, Malang

Create web UI design and turn designs into code.

Jul. 2015 - Mar. 2016

## Web Programer Intern @PT PLN, Surabaya

Developed a web app for monitoring servers using PHP with Codeigniter.

## **Education**

## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Informatics Engineering, Brawijaya University (GPA 3.7) 2012-2017, Malang

# Course/Bootcamp

**UX Research and Design Bootcamp** 

**Binar Academy** 

Digital Skills: User Experience

FutureLearn.com

Responsive Web Design

freecodecamp.org

Programming: HTML, CSS, JS

digitalent.kominfo.go.id

#### Contact

- mariani.workmail@gmail.com
- +6281235419940
- in mariani-mariani
- www.marianiweb.site

### **Skills**

## **Development**

HTML, CSS, SCSS Javascript, Java JQuery, ReactJs, GSAP Bootstrap, Primefaces MySQL

Wordpress

#### **Tools**

GIT, Sourcetree, Google Analytics, Trello, Figma, Maze, Photoshop, Adobe XD

## **Industry Knowledge**

Responsive UI

SEC

UX Design (design system, prototyping, usability testing)

Agile Development

# Language

Indonesia - Native English - TOEFL ITP 557